yazino.com 2012-10-27

# Yazino Privacy Policy

Yazino has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm belief and commitment to privacy.

The following statement details what information we obtain from you, how we use it and how we fulfill our obligations to protect your privacy. Please read it carefully. By using the Yazino site and its services, you will be agreeing that you are happy for Yazino to gather and use your information in the ways stated in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

#### Browsing the Sites

At Yazino we like to ensure that we will continue to meet the demands of our customers. To help us to understand your needs and improve the relevance of the services we offer you as an individual, we may collect anonymous information on your browsing activity while using Yazino's Services, such as IP address, browser type or referring URL.

You cannot be identified personally as a result of the information we collect while you use our Services and we mainly examine browsing activity to monitor aggregated site traffic and analyse it.

We may also provide anonymous statistics about user's activity to reputable third party vendors, but these will not include details that would allow the recipient to identify you.

#### Cookies

Internet cookies are common and do not harm your system - they just store or gather site information. They help you do things online, like remembering logon details so you don't have to re-enter them when revisiting a site. We use cookies to recognise returning visitors and to deliver content specific to your interests. We don't use cookies to track people's Internet usage after leaving our Sites and we don't store personal information in them that others could read and understand. We will not sell or distribute cookie information without your prior consent.

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many sites, including this one.

#### Joining Yazino

When you register with Yazino, subscribe to our Services, email notifications, newsletter, or request contact, there is certain information we collect to enable us to operate the Services. Details we may collect include name, address, telephone number and E-mail address.

When you use Yazino on your social network site, we may record information regarding the use of the Service, and may collect other information visible on your social network pages in accordance with the terms of use associated with those pages.

When you invite new members into your network or send messages through the Services, we may collect and maintain the information associated with those messages, including email addresses and content.

Yazino will never offer a third party access to this information for any purpose save that we will pass your contact information to services you have requested to be put in touch with, and Yazino will only store information necessary to operate effectively.

#### Personal Information

The personal information you submit to Yazino is held with the highest commitment to your privacy.

We believe that your privacy is important and have security in place to protect personal information, so far as is reasonably practicable, from loss, misuse or alteration. However, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet. You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential.

We may use your personal information to:-

1\. administer the Sites;

2\. improve your experience by personalising the Sites;

3\. enable your use of the Services available on the Sites;

4\. send to you general (non-marketing) communications;

5\. send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;

6\. send to you marketing communications which we think may be of interest to you (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications by contacting us via the Support page on our Sites; and

7\. deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the Sites.

If you purchase any virtual currency or virtual items, we can also use your information to:-

1\. send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you; and

2\. supply to you Services purchased via the Sites.

Yazino may disclose information about you to its partners in order to provide the Services, resolve service problems and correct errors in the Services, to communicate with you about the Services, to provide you with advertising and promotional information in connection with the Services, and to enhance your experience on the Services. However, we do not give our partners an independent right to share this information.

Due to our contractual obligations with these third parties and the need to share information to deliver and support the Services, we cannot provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of sharing information (whether Personally Identifiable Information or other information) with these third parties.

Yazino, certain of its partners, and each of their contractors and employees may view the Content that you transmit to the service to provide the Services and otherwise perform the tasks set forth in this Privacy Policy.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you:-

1\. to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

2\. in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

3\. in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to other for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and

4\. to the purchasers (or prospective purchasers) of any business or asset which we are selling or contemplating selling.

Except as provided for in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to any third parties.

Yazino may maintain copies of your content indefinitely, or delete certain content in whole or in part for any or no reason as Yazino in its absolute discretion determines.

Yazino does not store credit or debit card information.

#### Children under the age of 13

Yazino does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow them to register. If you are under the age of 13, please do not attempt to register with us or send us any personal information. No-one under the age of 13 is permitted to provide any personal information to or on Yazino.

If we learn that we have collected such information, Yazino will delete that information as soon as practicable.

If you believe that we have such information, please contact us immediately with the details.

#### Children between age of 13 and 18

Minors of 13 years and over should ask their parents or guardians for permission before providing any personal information to Yazino.

#### Public Information

Information about yourself you chose to share or post on the Yazino Sites is information for the public domain and therefore cannot be classed as private and it at your own discretion. If we request any information which could be classed as private, Sites will make you aware of this at the time of submission.

By submitting your information to Yazino, you give Yazino unconditional permission to use this information regardless of any moral rights, copyright, service mark, trademark or patent laws. Further, you allow absolutely Yazino to publish, modify, edit, delete, translate, distribute and otherwise reproduce the information in whatever format we choose.

#### Third party links

Yazino may contain links to other sites but we cannot assume responsibility for any other site's content or information handling practices. We urge you to review each site's privacy policy before using them.

Yazino does not accept any liability in connection with any third party website that can be accessed through this site and does not endorse or approve the content of any such website.

#### Policy Amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time to time by posting a new version on our Sites. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

We may also notify you of changes to this policy by email.

#### Your Consent

By using the Yazino Sites, you agree that you are happy for your information to be gathered and used in the ways described in this policy.

However, if you change your mind about the way you have agreed your data can be used, you can terminate your account at any time which will remove your profile and other personal information from view. Yazino, however, may (but is not obligated to) keep information about you that is on its system following your termination. Please contact Yazino to terminate your account or for any other questions about your personal information.

If you wish to amend any of the data we hold about you, just contact us via the website.

Please note that if you send messages or post material containing personal information, that information may be collected and used by others.

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you, for which we may charge the statutory allowable fee for provision of this information.

#### Transfer of Information

We reserve the right to transfer your personal information in the event of a transfer of ownership of Yazino or the acquisition of substantially all the assets of Yazino related to the business which collected such information, such as acquisition by or merger with another company. In such an event, Yazino will notify users who have provided email addresses when information about those users is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. Others' Information

You may decide to provide us with another person's email address so that person may be invited to join Yazino or so that we may facilitate your communication with other people through the Services.

You may also provide us with another person's contact information for purposes of delivering information through the Services. We use this information to contact and, if necessary, remind that person that he or she has been invited to join Yazino or received content through an Yazino. All invitees are provided with the option not to receive further invitations from Yazino. We may disclose such information if required to do so in order to comply with legal processes, as described above.

Yazino Limited is registered in Guernsey, Company Number 54245, Registered Office: Island House, Grande Rue, St Martins, Guernsey, GY4 6RU
